You're taking
a vacation from normalcy.
The setting, a weird motel where
the bed is stained with mystery,
and there's also some
mystery floating in the pool.
Your key card may not open
the exercise room
because someone smeared
mystery on the lock.
But it will open
the Scary Door.
Submitted for your
Emmy consideration,
a popular senator
with unpopular ideas.
There is no such thing
as space aliens!
Oh! How can you be
so sure
them aliens ain't
already among us?
I'll tell you how!
Because you are one!
Hey, I was watching that!
The Saints just needed
a field goal to tie!
Lrrr, you lazy ruler of the
planet Omicron Persei 8!
You said you would conquer a planet today,
but you have not even
shed your skin yet.
Yes, Ndnd. I heard you
the first hundred times.
I'll conquer
something tomorrow
after I fuel up on one of your
disgusting egg-white omelets.
You want yolks? Fine!
Enjoy your stroke.
I am conquering Erth!
Not so fast,
Invader X!
Here comes
Delivery-Boy Man!
Special deliver for Invader X! Laser eye power!
Hand magnet power!
Yay! I'm unbuckled!
Stop it, you hero!
Reverse-time power!
It's earlier now.
So? What do you
think of my comic?
Let me put it like this.
After I leave here,
I'm getting a memory enema.
If I might offer
some constructive criticism,
there was never
any real peril.
I mean, the delivery guy has,
like, 30 superpowers.
Well, that's because he was
bitten by a radioactive superman!
This is wonderful!
It is, isn't it?
Wait, those are the ads.
These X-ray specs will really
take the guesswork out of surgery.
No more chopping
blindly in the goop.
Don't waste your
allowance, Zoidberg.
This stuff is
butt-grade crap.
Amuse your friends
with real vomit!
Throw your voice!
Sea monkeys!
Throw your sea monkeys!
My disintegrator
ray really works!
But that's you.
That's how I know
it's bunkum.
The Farnsworth Novelty
Disintegrator Ray is nothing more
than a common teleporter ray.
Worthless toy!
I'm sick of being critiqued
by nitpicking nerds.
I'm taking this
to a comic book convention!
it's crowded!
Good thing everyone is
freshly bathed and groomed.
Oooh!
What are you doing? That's
the rare Zapp Brannigan
with recording
session blooper!
Don't tell me how to do the line. It sickens me.
But the sign said
there was a mint in the box.
Thank you so... Okay, thanks. Thanks so...
Settle down!
So, anyway, we're really excited to show
you guys the pilot for our new series.
It's set in the year 4000,
and we call it Futurella!
Wow. Fox has really
streamlined the process.
Matt will now
take questions.
But please, only about
Futurella,
not
The Simpsons.
Yes? The robot standing on
the small child over there?
Yeah, when are you
going to make
a second Simpsons movie?
Mr. Aragonйs, I'm a big fan of your cartoons
and your mustache.
You want it? Take it. It's
brought me nothing but misery.
Wow. Thanks!
If you could just
quiet down, I wanted
to get your opinion
of my comic book.
Seсor, anyone who still
writes comics is a hero to me.
Mmm. It stinks.
But, um, I do like the
tiny doodles in the margins.
Oh, that's just some relish
from a hot dog I found.
Attention,
ladies and gentleboys,
the costume contest
is about to begin.
The costume contest!
Yeah! Devo!
What the hell are
you supposed to be?
Every nerd's fantasy, baby.
Next up,
contestant number 36!
Contestant 36, everyone!
Next up, contestant...
I am Lrrr,
ruler of the planet...
Hold on a second,
let me just get this.
I am Lrrr, ruler of
the planet Omicron Persei 8.
You are hereby conquered!
Please line up
in order of how much beryllium
it takes to kill you!
Damn,
that's a good costume.
Next up, contestant 38!
I don't understand.
Why are the humans still eating their
soft pretzels instead of surrendering?
They're probably just
waiting for Joss Whedon.
Joss Whedon's here?
Wait a minute.
You look familiar.
Yeah,
you almost ate me once.
I was in your mouth
for five minutes.
Leela?
And the winner is
Nerdgasma!
Whoo!
I got fruit boobs!
What's the use?
Now what?
I send you out
to conquer a planet,
and all you bring back
is J.J. Abrams' face?
I thought you'd like it.
You haven't
even tried it on.
I might dress up in a face if
you ever took me anywhere nice!
Oh, boy, here we go.
I built this castle
with my own two slaves!
What are you
gonna do, kick me out?
I am Lrrr, ruler of the planet Omicron Persei 8!
May I crash on your couch?
So he just showed up unannounced,
raided the liquor cabinet,
sprayed urine on the ceiling
and passed out?
And the walls.
Leave me alone.
My wife hates me and planetary
conquest has become a chore.
There, there. You're just having a midlife crisis.
Midlife crisis, eh?
Lrrr demands the comfort of
pop-psychological platitudes!
Look, hoss,
your wife threw you out.
That's your license
to be a jerk.
Do whatever
the hell you want,
then walk away
and light a cigar.
Don't listen to him, Lrrr.
Bender may seem happy
but long-term,
you need to reinvest
in your relationship
with Ndnd.
Yes, it's clear
what I must do.
I like it.
I'm thinking we
need to downplay
those hideous
growths on your head.
Horns are a sign of virility.
Also, they house my testes.
I'm thinking horn extensions.
You need
some arm candy.
It's the perfect accessory for
out-of-shape middle-aged creeps like you.
Yeah, I said it!
What's your type, Borgnine?
Big and angry.
Look, brah,
you're just not gonna find
a lot of hot, gigantic
Omicronian babes
in this solar system.
There's one!
Hey, cool cape.
Where'd you get that?
What, this old thing?
I murdered my father.
My name's Lrrr, ruler of
the planet Omicron Persei 8.
I am called Grrl.
Of the planet
Omicron Persei 8?
That is a pretty name!
What's on the TV tonight?
Oh, wait! I don't care,
because I got a date!
I know it's not
what you want to hear,
but I think
this is a mistake.
Leela's right.
That's not what
you want to hear.
What you want to hear is
that I fixed my comic book.
Now the hero is
more relatable
because he has no
ridiculous powers.
Let's watch, shall we?
One more step
and little Miss Constructive
Criticism here gets it!
Oh, yeah? I may be just a simple
delivery boy with no superpowers,
so there's nothing I can do.
Okay.
So? Give me
your honest praise.
Fry, I've now seen two
comic books, so listen to me.
Why should I care about the
hero when all he does is cry?
Hmm. That dinner
was a worthy foe.
Yes, we shall not
see its like again.
So, um...
Um, I'm sorry. I haven't
done this for a while.
I just got partway out
of a bad relationship.
Maybe I should
take this off.
You're a human?
Only physically.
I'm a cross-species dresser.
Wait, you're an
actual Omicronian?
Oh, God. Oh, God,
what have I done?
This is so hot!
Conquer me, Lrrr!
Sharpen your horns
on my scaly thorax!
I want to go home!
But Ndnd would
never take me back now.
Ndnd just wants
what every she-beast wants,
to feel like you're
listening to her nagging.
Is there anything she's been
riding your ass about?
Conquering things, I guess.
I could conquer Earth,
kill all humans.
That's a thought.
No!
We don't need
a war of the worlds.
That's it! We need
a war of the worlds!
I'll call Orson Welles.
Dork calling Orson!
You're asking me,
the renowned spokesman
for Paul Masson wine,
to recreate my brilliant
1938 radio broadcast
merely to deceive and impress
the wife of this skinny reptile?
Sorry. Never mind.
I'll do it for free.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we interrupt our program
of The Jonas Brothers
and their orchestra
to bring you
a special bulletin.
We interrupt our program of The
Jonas brothers and their orchestra
to bring you
a special bulletin.
I'm speaking to you from the hickory
farms in Grover's Mall, New Jersey,
through a mouthful
of summer sausage,
mmm, where I hardly
know where to begin. Mmm!
A huge spacecraft, piloted
by a devastatingly handsome...
Now, how in God's name
do I know
what the fellow looks like
if he's inside a ship
miles in the air?
It's just foolish
on its face.
If you want the cheese log,
you'll read what I wrote.
Very well.
I shall comply.
I'm getting reports
that cities across the globe
are being destroyed
by this noble invader,
whose good looks are apparently
discernible across vast distances
and through solid metal.
But wait, the leader of the attack
is swaggering out of his ship
and up to a convenient
nearby microphone.
Now, why couldn't I have just
described his appearance at this point?
This is the type of
thing I'm talking about.
People of Earth, I am Lrrr,
conqueror of your planet.
Cue screams.
You will now
remove your skulls
and play dodgeball with them
for my amusement!
Ooh! I could swear
his horns have gotten longer!
Sir, I've intercepted
an Earth broadcast.
Put it up on the Zenith.
Oh, God!
Earth is conquered,
the destruction
of civilization complete.
Now stay tuned for
Little Orphan Annie.
To hell with Little Orphan Annie
! We've got to do something.
What's that, honey?
How many dead?
I don't know, 80 million?
Okay. I love you, too.
That was Ndnd.
She's taking me back!
I'm sorry I've
been so difficult.
So, you thought you could
conquer us so easily, eh?
Nice job. We surrender.
Earth is yours.
Damn, I'm good.
Now, may I please
have that cheese log?
O glorious conqueror, permit
me to offer up a sacrifice.
How about this?
Hey!
Yeah, he'll do.
Come on, Lrrr.
Show's over.
Fine, okay.
About this conquering thing,
funny story...
Hello, Lrrr.
Lrrr! Put a stop
to this right now!
Okay! Okay! Quit nagging!
Lrrr, why are you yelling softly
with the purple-furred one?
Uh, it's nothing, my queen.
He messed up my hair.
I'm missing a leg!
We fought like hell, sir,
but in the end, we caved like
a house of soufflй cards.
Got it.
Peace with honor.
Well, I resign again.
Come, Nixon.
Introduce me to
the kitchen staff.
I must lay down the law
about Lrrr's low-sodium diet.
You've got to
tell her the truth.
And lay off
the salted peanuts!
I'm just trying to get the
leg taste out of my mouth.
Lrrr! I'm in here now,
not out there!
Give me a little time.
With a lady like Ndnd,
one must use finesse.
Coming, gigantums!
Mmm. That's crisp.
Yes, but no more so
than your squamous dorsal plates in the moonlight.
I am experiencing arousal.
My organs are
moving into position.
Ndnd, there's something
I've got to tell you.
What is it?
Is there someone else?
What? No, no, it's about this takeover of Earth.
It's... It's...
The spark that
reignited our marriage?
Yes! Exactly.
Good night.
Oh, lord. Now what?
I couldn't tell
her the truth.
Look, you scaly crybaby,
you do what I say
and you do it now!
I knew it!
Frying pans!
Cast-iron frying pans!
It's not what
it looks like!
What do I do?
Do what I say.
Tell her!
Tell me what?
Give me the heavy one.
The invasion was all a fake.
I just wanted to impress you.
You lied?
What else have you
been hiding from me?
What else? Nothing else.
I still want you, Lrrr,
and I'm willing
to fight for you.
All I got left is
a colander and a pie pan.
Lrrr?
Look, we only had one date.
I barely mated with her.
Whatever. I harbor no resentment against her.
What I want to know
is what is up between you
and Bossy Boots here.
Her?
She's just a bossy friend.
Exactly!
She nagged you, tormented you
and pushed you around.
That is my job!
This must be settled.
I demand the ancient ritual of
Rrrmrrrmrrrfrrrmrrr or Consequences!
Rrrmrrrmrrrfrrrmrrr or what?
Let the ritual begin!
The rules are the same
as in the home version.
Lrrr must simply choose
between myself and Leela...
Fine. Hurry up.
...by shooting
the one he rejects.
Lrrr, I'm getting angry.
Don't you go
through with this.
She is not the boss of you!
I am the boss of you!
Um... Oh...
Leela's going to die!
What would
Delivery-Boy Man do?
I do not want
to shoot anybody.
You never want
to do anything!
Oh, nag, nag, nag.
You want me to stop nagging?
Then shoot me!
Oh, you'd like that,
wouldn't you?
Beats staring at your
fat ass on the couch!
Oh, yeah? I'll show you!
Ray-blocking power!
Fry!
Lrrr! You were willing to
shoot that bossy temptress!
You really do value my nagging above all others!
Good night, dumb prince.
Come back, Lrrr!
I want to have
your popplers!
There'll never
be anyone but you!
Hello.
Of course I'll marry you.
Wait,
what the shmell happened?
I thought Ndnd disintegrated
you with this ray gun.
It's just
a cheap teleporter.
I bought it out of the back
of a comic book.
Cha-ching!
The teleporter gun? That
means Fry might still be...
Fry!
Fry?
Is this him?
Fry! You're alive!
Not only that,
I now know exactly
how to end my comic book.
Let's watch.
Say good-bye
to your forehead,
because I'm going
to shoot you in it!
Not if I leap in
front of your death ray,
and I am going to do that.
Jumping sound! Ow!
I didn't shoot yet.
As usual, your delivery
arrived too soon.
Oh, Delivery-Boy Man! You
saved me by random chance!
Don't thank random chance.
Thank my
meteor-wishing power,
with your lips.
Good ending.
Not great.